- [Instructor] Okay, so now let's work on the put endpoint,
which will allow us to update a single player.
So again, like we've done before,
what we're going to do first is work on the controller.
So what we want to do first is export a function
that will be the update for the player.
So let's go ahead and call this one updatePlayer,
and again, it's going to be an async function.
Request, response.
And we're going to try again,
and then we're going to do the exact same thing.
So copy the catch,
paste it here like so,
and then we're going to write what we're going to do.
So there's going to be a little bit more code on this one
because we need to update a player
that we're going to pass inside of that controller.
So again, let's create a player,
and what we'll do, we'll await,
and what we'll use on Mongoose,
we'll use find oneOneAndUpdate, this one here,
and this is going to need a few things.
So first of all, we're going to need to pass an ID,
and we're going to pass it from the params
like we've done before to get a single ID.
So we're going to call this PlayerId,
and then we're going to have whatever
in the body of the requests,
what we want to change.
And then finally, if it's a brand new,
or if we can't find that specific player in the database,
then this will return a new document.
And then like before, we need to get a response back
just to make sure
that we've updated the player in this case.
Okay, so that basically is
what your controller's going to look like.
So save this,
and now what we need to do is add in the controllers
that we're passing here.
So updatePlayer,
and then what we're going to do is use this specific route here
because we need to pass in the params the player ID,
so we're going to do a put method
and we're going to use the updatePlayerController,
and that's basically what we need.
So this will update a specific player.
Okay, so let's make sure our server is running,
so let's bring up the terminal.
Bring, let's make sure we are in the backend, npm start.
Make sure everything is running properly.
So again, you need a specific player,
so we're going to need to go into our documents first.
So let's go in Studio 3T,
and I'm just going to run this
to make sure that I have all my players here.
So I don't like this name here, so let's copy this.
Value as text, this guy here.
And then let's go back to Postman,
and what I'm going to do is paste the player ID,
and you need to go in the body.
You need to use form URL encoded.
And as you can see, in the last time,
we had all these things here,
so what I'm going to do
is change the first name, last name, and email to...
Let's go back here just to see what the data was.
I'm just going to change it to my own name,
and do three for the email, just for reference,
so you can see what's happening here, too.
Okay, so Manny Henry,
and let's do Henry with a Y
just to make a bit of a change here,
and let's do three, me3@methree.com.
And you know what?
While we're at it, let's change the phone number to seven.
Okay, so you need to change the method,
'cause this is not a get method, it's a put method,
so as we coded it,
it's the put method using this endpoint.
So we're passing the actual ID, and then we're sending it,
and then as you can see,
this particular ID has changed with Henry Manny,
and you can check this directly in the database,
but this is proof enough that it has worked.
So if you want to check further, you're going to see it.
I even changed the first name to Henry
and last name to Manny.
So this is all good.
We've made the changes and that endpoint is working,
so let's move on.